wi-fi.org 2019-12-07

# Wi-Fi Alliance Privacy Policy | Wi-Fi Alliance

Your right to privacy is very important. We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. We will not provide any of your personal information to other companies or individuals without your permission. Below is a summary of our policy. Website users who are located in the European Economic Area (EEA) should review our GDPR Privacy Notice, which supplements this general Wi-Fi Alliance Privacy Policy. 

**Automatic Collection of Information**

The information we collect automatically is used to improve the content of our website, and any web browser cookies we deploy are only used to collect aggregate statistics that helps us measure the effectiveness of our website content as well as our navigational design. We do not use cookies to track individual information. Please see our [Cookies Notice](https://www.wi-fi.org/gdpr-privacy-notice#Cookies) for more information about the cookies that we use.

**Collection of Voluntarily Submitted Information**

Wi-Fi Alliance collects the email addresses of those who communicate with us by email, and the email addresses provided by visitors voluntarily completing our online web forms, such as a membership application, survey, document requests, meeting registrations and other website subscriptions.

Wi-Fi Alliance collects the postal address and telephone numbers provided by visitors voluntarily completing any of our online web forms, such as a membership application, survey, document requests, meeting registrations and other website subscriptions.

We will not provide any of your personal information to other companies or individuals without your permission. However, we may need to provide your name and delivery address to third parties that Wi-Fi Alliance uses for the purposes of delivering specific services to you (e.g., customer support, or a shipping company if you have asked us to send something to you.)

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website.

**Security**

We take appropriate steps to protect your privacy and implement reasonable security measures to protect your personal information in storage. We use secure transmission methods to collect personal data such as website passwords.

Any information you have access to via Wi-Fi Alliance systems, such as other members’ email addresses, must be used for Wi-Fi Alliance business purposes only. It is strictly forbidden to use Wi-Fi Alliance contacts for any external gain, including sending product marketing or company promotions.  Providing Wi-Fi Alliance members’ contact information to third parties is strictly forbidden, unless you have documented express consent from the Wi-Fi Alliance member in question. 

**Control of Your Information**

You can help Wi-Fi Alliance maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying us of any changes to your address, title, company name, phone number or email address. Wi-Fi Alliance members may update their contact information on the Members-Only website or by contacting Wi-Fi Alliance staff.

Website visitors may opt-in to receive updates regarding press releases, events and other information. We give you the opportunity to change your election to receive/not receive information from us. At any time, a user may opt-out of receiving event updates, press release announcements, and other information and updates from Wi-Fi Alliance by updating your profile or by sending an email request to [GDPR@wi-fi.org](mailto:GDPR@wi-fi.org).

Our website may provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control those websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third party websites.

**How to Contact Us**

Wi-Fi Alliance  
10900-B Stonelake Boulevard, Suite 126  
Austin, TX 78759  USA  
Email: [website@wi-fi.org](mailto:website@wi-fi.org)  
Last update: September 2019
